question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Destiny,&quot; the three subclasses of the Hunter are Bladedancer, Nightstalker, and Sunsinger.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Kerbol System (from Kerbal Space Program) includes a Saturn analogue.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
